好吧
All right.
你已经搞定了
You're done.
接下来我们讲讲我是如何解决这个问题的。
Let's talk about how I solved this one.
我们先返回来看看你刚刚写的service代码
Let's take a look at the sunshine
service you just wrote.
首先，我们需要一些常量，如LOG_TAG
To begin with, it's useful to have
some constants, a log tag, so
这样我们就知道它是如何工作的了
we can actually see
how it's functioning.
然后是这个LOCATION_QUERY_EXTRA
And most importantly,
this location query extra.
我们通过这个LOCATION_QUERY_EXTRA
We use this location query extra
to pass the location query.
在我们的Intents Service中传递地点请求数据
Into our Intents service.
我们把从fetchWeatherTask的doInBackground方法中
In onHandleIntent, we actually put
the code that we had in do in background
提取的代码放到onHandleIntent中。
in our fetch weather task.
但你也能发现我们唯一所能得到的参数只是一个intent
However, as you can see the only
parameter we get is an intent.
这里通过stringExtra将地点请求数据提取出来
So we pull the location
query out of a stringExtra.
这里就用到了Location_Query_Extra字符串
Using the location query extra string.
我们从fetchWeatherTask中把其它代码拷贝出来
We can copy the rest of the code
from fetch weather task here
因为Intent Service也能创建一个helper线程来执行代码
because intent service also
creates a helper thread for
这个功能和AsyncTask所做的类似
us to run code on,
similar to what async task does.
注意我们也要处理所有和mContext相关的代码
Note that we also fix up all of
the code that refers to m context.
作为服务，它也有自己的上下文（Context）
As a service, also has its own context.
最后我们需要从forecast fragment中的updateWeather
The final thing we do,
is call our service from update weather,
调用我们的服务
with in forecast fragment.
我们把地点请求作为extra来处理
We simply put an extra for
而不是作为参数来传递
the location query,
instead of using it as a parameter.
然后启动服务
And then start the service.
然后删掉fetchWeatherTask,以及和它相关的代码
Then we can delete the fetch weather
task, and its associated test.